[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Hello everyone, and welcome
&gt;&gt; 大家好欢迎你们
to Building Apps with Dynamic
来到 Building Apps with Dynamic
Type.
Type（使用动态字体构建 app）
My name is Clare, and together
我叫 Clare
with my colleague Nandini, I'm
和我的同事 Nandini
excited to share with you how
很高兴能够与你们分享
you can make your apps work
如何能让你的 app
great at any text size.
在任何字体大小下都看起来很好
Today we'll first cover what
今天我们先谈谈
Dynamic Type is and why the
什么是 Dynamic Type 以及为什么
feature exists.
提出这个功能
Next we'll look at what's new in
接着我们将会看到
iOS 11 for Dynamic Type.
在 iOS 11 中 Dynamic Type 有什么新的进步
We'll follow that with some
再之后我们会看到一些
guidelines and API you can apply
参考指导和你们可用使用的 API
to your own apps, and finally
用到你自己的 app 中最后
we'll show all of that hands-on
我们会展示所有这些
in a sample app.
在一个示例 app 中是怎么做的
So first what is Dynamic Type.
首先什么是 Dynamic Type
Dynamic Type is a feature that
Dynamic Type 是一个
allows users to customize the
允许用户在屏幕上自定义
size of text on screen.
字体大小的功能
For example, some users may
比如有些用户可能
prefer a smaller text size so
喜欢更小的字体
they can fit more content on
这样他们可以在屏幕上看到更多内容
Others may prefer a larger text
有些人可能会喜欢更大的字体
size because it's more
因为它会
comfortable to read.
读起来更舒服
But Dynamic Type goes beyond a
但是 Dynamic Type 不仅仅限于
user's preferences.
用户的偏好
Some users may experience eye
很多用户可能感受过
strain when viewing text at the
眼睛干涩当他们在
default size for long periods of
默认字号下阅读很长时间之后
Others may simply have less
有些人可能只是
acute vision due to aging.
由于年纪增长而视力下降
And yet others may have a low
而有的人可能是
vision condition which makes it
视力情况很差导致
impossible for them to read text
他们几乎无法阅读
at the default size.
默认字号的文字
So for these users Dynamic Type
对于这些用户 Dynamic Type
isn't just a preference, it's an
就不仅仅是一种偏好
actual need and by supporting
而是一种实际需求通过
Dynamic Type in your apps, you
让你的 app 支持 Dynamic Type
can allow these users to use
你可以允许这些用户使用
your app and have a great
你的 app 并且获得很好的
experience with it.
用户体验
The Dynamic Type settings can be
Dynamic Type 的设置
found in the Settings app under
在“设置”下的
Display and Brightness.
“显示和亮度”中
It starts out with seven
它最开始有
different text sizes you can
其中不同的字体大小你可以
choose from, and the default one
从中选择默认字体
is in the middle.
在中间
You can also go into your
你可以到你的
Accessibility settings and there
“辅助功能”设置中
you can enable five even larger
使用五个更大字体
Those sizes are geared towards
这些字体是为
users with low vision.
视力不好的用户设计的
They range from somewhat larger
这些字体从
than default size to much
比默认稍微大点到特别大都有
Now, looking at this you might
现在看到这个你可能会
be wondering whether you really
想你到底是不是
need text to get that big.
需要字体变的这么大
Let's look in the example of why
我们来看一个例子
this is useful.
看看它为什么是有用的
So here's the phone app and on
这是一个手机 app
the left we've got it at the
左边我们是把它
largest size, not including the
放大成最大字号不包括
Accessibility sizes.
“辅助功能”设置里的大小
On the right we have it at the
在右边的我们把它设置成了
larger size overall.
更大的字体
Now let's look at this through
现在我们从
the lens of a user with low
视力差的人的视角来看
Someone with low vision might
视力差的人看事物
see something closer to what we
比我们看事物的距离要近一些
Notice how the version on the
请看到左边的版本
left is completely unreadable,
已经完全无法阅读了
but the version on the right is
但是右边的版本
still fairly readable, even
还是可以看清楚的尽管
though its blurry.
是字迹模糊的.
So text size makes a huge
所以字体大小可以很大程度的
difference for the legibility of
对你的 app 的可读性造成影响
your apps and that's why it's
这就是为什么
really important that you
你的 app 需要
support the full range of
支持所有的
Dynamic Type sizes.
Dynamic Type 字体
So that's what Dynamic Type is,
这就是 Dynamic Type
and now let's look at what's new
现在我们来看一看
in iOS 11 for Dynamic Type.
在 iOS 11 中 Dynamic Type 有什么新的进步
The biggest thing that's changed
最大的改变是
is that Dynamic Type support is
Dynamic Type 已经被
vastly improved and expanded
广泛的提高了并应用于
across all of iOS.
所有的 iOS 设备
When we started working on iOS
当我们开始开发 iOS
11, we had three goals in mind.
11时我们有三个目标
First, text should be large
第一字体必须足够大
enough for the user to read.
让用户能够阅读
In other words, text should
换句话说文字必须和
scale with Dynamic Type.
Dynamic Type 大小一致
Second, the text should be fully
第二文字必须可辨认度很高
It shouldn't be truncated
它不可以有不必要的截断
unnecessarily and it shouldn't
也不可以
be overlapped or clipping.
发生重叠或被剪切
And third, we want an app UI to
第三我们希望得到一个 app 的 UI
look beautiful at all text
在任何字体大小下都看起来美观
Now, for more information on the
如果想了解更多关于
design thinking behind the iOS
新一代 iOS11 的 Dynamic Type
11 Dynamic Type improvements,
背后的设计理念
please check out the Design for
请查看昨天的 Design for
Everyone talk from yesterday.
Everyone 演讲
So now let's look at some
现在我们来看一些例子
examples of what's changed.
看看我们改变了什么
Here's the Settings app.
这是设置 app
Notice how it now adapts
请注意它是如何
beautifully for all the text
完美适应各种字体大小的
Here's another example from
这是另一个例子“日历”
Notice how text everywhere is
请看所有的文字是
scaling with Dynamic Type, and
随着 Dynamic Type 缩放的
some texts, like the event time,
有些文字比如事件时间
is laid out differently to
使用了不同的构图
accommodate larger text.
来适应更大的字体
Now, there are some cases where
有些情况下
we don't scale for Dynamic Type.
我们不需要与 Dynamic Type 一致
For example, in tab bars, if we
比如在选项卡栏中如果我们
were to scale a text here, the
把这里的字体放大
tab bar would take away too much
选项卡栏会占用
room from the main content.
主要内容太多的空间
However, now, in iOS 11, if you
但是现在在 in iOS 11 中如果你
have one of the five largest
选择了
Dynamic Type settings chosen,
Dynamic Type 设置中五个大字体之一
you can long press on one of the
你可以长按其中的
items in the tab bar.
一个按钮
For example, the Voicemail tab,
比如语音信箱选项
and that will show a larger
我们会有一个更大的
version in the middle of the
图标显示在屏幕中间
So that's a sampling of what's
这是对 iOS11 中改变的内容的
changed in iOS 11.
一些举例
Now let's look at some
现在我们来看一些
guidelines in API that you can
API 的使用说明你们可以
apply to your own apps.
用到自己的 app 中
We'll be covering this in four
我会从四个方面来谈
First, we'll look at how you can
首先我们先来看如何
scale your font sizes for
将你的字体大小与
Dynamic Type.
Dynamic Type 缩放一致
Second, we'll see how you can
第二我们来看你如何
accommodate larger text in your
把更大字体放入
app's layouts.
你的 app 的界面中
Third, we'll look at the
第三我们会看一个
specific, very common case of
表示图的具体的常见的例子
And then finally, we'll even see
最后我们将会看到
how images can work well with
图像如何和
Dynamic Type.
Dynamic Type 完美共处
So first, let's scale font sizes
那么首先我们先将字体
for Dynamic Type.
缩放到 Dynamic Type
The easiest way to do this is to
最简单的方法就是
use the built-in text styles
使用 iOS 内置的文本样式
Here's a list of all of our text
这是一个我们全部的文本
styles, along with their font
样式的清单还有它们
sizes at the default text size.
在默认设置下的字体大小
If your user has a different
如果你的用户选择了
text size selected, these font
另一个字体大小这些字体的
sizes will also change.
大小也会改变
Now, for those of you who have
对于已经
already be using text styles in
在你的 app 中使用了文本样式的人
your app, first, thank you; and
首先谢谢你们
second, there's one important
其次在 iOS 11 中有一个
change in iOS 11 that you should
重要的改变你们需要
be aware of.
加以注意
Prior to iOS 11 all the text
在 iOS 11 之前所有的文本
style adapted for the seven
样式都适用七种
standard sizes.
标准大小
However, only the body style
然而只有正文内容的样式
adapted for the five
会适用五种
accessibility sizes.
辅助功能中的大小
In iOS 11 all of the text style
在 iOS 11 中所有的文本样式
adapt for all 12 text sizes.
都适用所有的12中文字大小
And so if you're using text
因此如果你在使用我们的文本样式
styles, you'll get support for
你将可以免费获得
all 12 sizes for free.
所有12种字体的支持
To use text styles in Interface
如果想在 Interface
Builder, go to the Attribute
Builder 里使用文本样式进入 Attribute
Inspector and change the font on
Inspector 然后在你的视图中选择更改字体
By default this will be
默认情况下这会是
something like System 17 point,
系统中的17号字
which means it's not going to
意思是它不会根据
scale with Dynamic Type.
Dynamic Type 而更改
But if you click on that T icon,
但你如果点击那个“T”按钮
you can choose one of the text
你就可以选择一个文本样式
style fonts instead and those
这些样式会进行缩放
Also, new in iOS 11 you can
另外在 iOS 11 中你可以
check the Automatically Adjust
勾选 Automatically Adjust
Font checkbox.
Font 选项
This means that if the user
这意味着如果用户
changes their text size while
更改了他们的字体大小
your app is running, your view
而你的 app 正在运行时
will automatically update its
你的界面会自动更新它的字体
font for the new text size.
让它变成新的字体大小
So we highly recommend you check
所以我们强烈建议你
this on all of your views.
在你的所有界面都勾选这个选项
In code it's just as easy to use
在代码中使用文本样式也很方便
You can use the
你可以使用
preferredFont(forTextStyle) API
preferredFont(forTextStyle) API
to get a font for the text
为文本样式获取一个字体
style, and then you can use the
然后你可以使用
adjustsFontForContentSize
adjustsFontForContentSize
Category property to make sure
Category 属性来确保
that your views update their
你的界面会更新字体
fonts if the text size changes.
当文字大小发生改变时
But what if you can't use text
但是如果你不能使用文本样式时怎么办？
Maybe you have a design that
也许你的设计
requires custom fonts.
要求使用自定义字体
The great news is that in iOS 11
好消息是在 iOS 11 中
it's really easy to get those
你可以很轻易的获得那些
fonts to work well with Dynamic
跟 Dynamic Type 可以完美适应的字体
So let's say you have some code
比如说你有一些代码
that assigns the font property
把字体属性赋值给了
of a label to a custom font of
一个标签用来自定义
your choosing.
你所选择的字体
In iOS 11 you can now use the
在 iOS 11 中你可以使用
new UIFontMetrics class to scale
全新的 UIFontMetrics 类来缩放
that font so that it will get
那个字体使它可以
smaller or bigger, depending on
变大或变小取决于
the user's text size.
用户的字体大小
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
Thanks.
谢谢
In this example we're using the
在这个例子中我们使用了
default font metrics, which
默认的字体规格
means we're using the font
也就是说我们使用了
metrics of the body text style.
正文文字样式的字体规格
That means that if body text
这就意味着正文文字
would be 50 percent larger for a
对于某个用户来说可能放大了百分之五十
particular user, your font will
而你的字体同时
also get 50 percent larger.
也会放大百分之五十
For better results, you can pick
如果想效果更好你可以选择
a particular text style that you
一种特定的文字样式
want to scale your font with.
让你的字体与之一致
So, for example, if you have a
那么举个例子如果你有一种
font that you're using for title
字体你用它作为
text in your app, you might
你的 app 的标题文字的样式你可能
choose to scale it in the same
会选择使用
way that we've scaled title1
我们缩放 title1 的方式来处理它
Now, a final word on web views.
关于网页界面的最后一点说明
Many of you may have web views
你们很多人可能都有网页界面
that you're displaying in your
在你的 iOS app 中展示
You should make those adapt for
你应该使它们也适应
Dynamic Type as well.
Dynamic Type
To do so, you can use the
要做到这一点你可以使用
-apple-system-body font and that
-apple-system-body 字体
will get you the body text style
它会让你获得正文样式字体
font and it will adapt for the
能适应用户的
user's dynamic typesetting.
动态排版
Now, note that this is only
请注意这只可以
available on Apple devices, so
在苹果设备上使用
if you're planning to use the
如果你想在
same web page for other
别的平台上使用同样的网页
platforms, make sure you set an
你要确保你已经
appropriate fallback font.
正确设置了备用字体
Then for your other styles you
然后对于你的其他样式
can define their font sizes in
你可以定义它们的字体大小
terms of relative units, and
通过相对单元调整然后
that way they'll scale
这样它们就会相应地缩放了
So that's how you can scale your
这就是你怎样
font sizes for Dynamic Type.
为 Dynamic Type 缩放字体的方法
Now let's look at how you can
现在我们来看一看你如何才能
accommodate larger text in your
在你的 app 界面中容纳更大的字体
So let's say we've got some text
比如说我们现在有一些
at the default text size, and
默认大小的文字
you can imagine that the white
你可以把这些白色的边框
border is the available area on
想像成在屏幕上的可用区域
So first step, let's scale the
那么第一步我们首先缩放字体
We have a problem.
我们遇到了一个问题
The text is now running off
现在文字超出了屏幕范围
screen and so your users are not
而你的用户将无法
going to see anything outside of
看到白色边框外的任何内容
To prevent the label from
为了让文字不超出
running off screen, we can add a
屏幕我们可以增加一个
trailing constraint.
尾部约束条件
But now we still have a problem
但现在我们还是遇到了问题
because the text is getting
因为文字被截断了
The end result is that your
结果是
users aren't going to see all
你的用户将不能看到
the text.
所有的文字
To really fix this let's wrap
要真正解决这个问题我们
the text and that will allow the
把文字自动分行这样就可以
text to grow as much as it needs
让文字要变多大就变多大
while still displaying all of
而且可以全部显示出来
To wrap text in Interface
要在 Interface
Builder you can use the
Builder 实现文字自动换行你可以使用
Attribute Inspector and adjust
Attribute Inspector 然后
the Lines property on your
在你的标签中调整 Lines 属性
By default this is set to one
默认情况下它被设置为
line, but if you change it to 0,
一行但你如果把它设为 0
that will allow your label to
它就允许你的文字
wrap to as many lines as it
自动换成内容
needs for its content.
所需要的行数
You can do the same thing in
你也可以用代码做
code by setting the number of
通过将 Lines 属性的
lines property to 0.
数目设为 0
Okay. Let's look at another
好的我们来看另一个
common scenario that can occur.
经常发生的情况
So when you're writing your app
当你在写你的 app 时
and you're thinking about the
你会想到
default text size, it's tempting
默认字体大小
to use constant values for your
你可能很想把间距设为一个恒定值
So you might have something like
所以你可能会得到
two labels here whose baselines
这样的两个标签它们的基线
are separated by a constant 40
之间的距离是恒定的 40
Looks great at the default text
这在默认字体下看着不错
size, but once you start
但是一旦你开始
adapting for Dynamic Type, you
适用 Dynamic Type
can run into problems like this,
你就可能会遇到这样的问题
where the labels overlap.
文字会发生重合
What we really want here is a
我们真正需要的是一种
spacing that's dynamic and that
动态的间距
accounts for the fonts involved.
可以应对各种字体
In iOS 11 you can now do this
在 iOS 11 中你可以通过
with new Auto Layout System
新的 Auto Layout System
Spacing Constraints.
Spacing Constraints 来完成
You can define the spacing
你可以在两个基线之间
between two baselines and Auto
定义间距而 Auto
Layout will automatically figure
Layout 会自动找出
out the best spacing to use
最适合的间距 out
based on the fonts of your
依据你的用户所用的字体
Now, if you try this and you
现在如果你试试这个
decide that you want a slightly
你决定你想要一个稍微
larger or smaller spacing, you
大一点或者小一点的间距
can do that, too, by adjusting
你也可以得到只需要调整
the Multiplier property and that
Multiplier 属性然后它会
will let you get the exact
让你获得你所需要的
results you want.
确切结果
It's also possible to use these
你也可以
new Auto Layout Constraints in
把 Auto Layout Constraints 用在
Interface Builder, and for more
Interface Builder 中
information on that, please
关于此的更多信息请 information on that please
check out the Auto Layout
查看今天早上的 the Auto Layout
Techniques and Interface Builder
Techniques and Interface Builder
talk that happened this morning.
讨论
Now, I know there are probably
现在我知道
some of you out there who have a
在你们当中有些人的
view in your app that was
app 的界面是
written eight or nine years ago
八九年前写的
and it's just not using Auto
没有使用 Auto Layout
Don't worry, we have you
不用担心我们帮你解决
So let's say you have some
比如说你有
layout code that sets a constant
一些界面的代码设置了一个
value and ads that to a y
恒定值并添加到一个 y origin
Using the same UIFontMetrics
使用我们之前看到的 UIFontMetrics
class we saw earlier we can
类我们可以
scale that 40 point value, or
缩放这个40 点的值或
any CGFloat value, and that way
任何 CGFloat 的值这样
it will get smaller or larger,
它就会变小或变大
depending on the user's text
取决于用户的字体大小
Now let's look at one final
现在我们来看最后一个
common scenario.
常见情况
Here we've got two labels that
现在两个标签
are side-by-side at the default
并排着且都是
text size.
默认字体大小
Again, you can imagine that the
你可以把那个
yellow border is the area
黄色边框想象成
available on screen.
屏幕上的可用区域
Now let's scale our font sizes.
现在我们缩放字体大小
As you can see, there's not
正如你所看到的那样
enough room for the text
屏幕上没有足够的空间了
anymore, so going back to what
那么回到
we saw earlier, we could try to
我们之前看到的我们可以
wrap the text --
试图让文字换行
and we'll get something like
我们会得到一个这样的情况
So I'd like to step back for a
那么我想要暂停一下
second and revisit those three
然后回顾一下
goals we mentioned at the
我们在开始时提到的
beginning of the talk.
三个目标
First, all text should be large
首先所有文字都必须足够大到
enough to read.
可以阅读
We've got that covered.
我们已经解决了这个问题
Second, all text should be fully
第二所有的文字必须可读性很高
That's true here.
这也达到了
None of the text is missing.
没有丢失什么文字
Third, app UI should look
第三 app 的界面必须
beautiful at all text sizes.
在任何字体大小下都看着美观
And that's where we haven't
在这一点我们还没有
quite met our goals yet.
达到目标
As you can see, on the righthand
正如你所看到的那样在右手边
side the d is being orphaned
字母 d 被和
from the rest of the word and it
单词的其他部分孤立开来
just doesn't look right.
这样看起来不对
So for this scenario we
对于这种情况
recommend that for larger font
我们建议对于较大的字体
sizes you change your layout to
可以更改你的界面
use vertical stacking and that
使用垂直叠加的方式
way each label can grow to the
这样每个标签都可以变得
full width of the screen.
跟屏幕宽度一致
Now, this technique works not
现在这个技术不仅仅可以
just for text, but for anything
用在文字上也可以用在
that might take room away from
任何可能占用文字空间的事物
For example, here's the Siri
比如说这是一个 Siri
Help screen and notice how on
Help 的屏幕你可以看到
the left, at the default text
在左边在默认的字体大小下
size, there's an icon that takes
有一个标志
up a horizontal column away from
在水平方向占掉了一栏
So that's why for larger font
这就是为什么在更大字体下
sizes we actually move that icon
我们就把这个标志移动到
above the text and allow the
文字的上方这样就允许了
text to grow to the full width
文字变得占满
of the screen.
整个屏幕宽度
Now, to do an alternate layout
要想设计一个这样的备用界面
based on the user's text size
取决于用户的字体大小
you'll need to know how to get
你需要知道怎样得到这个界面
You can do that by accessing the
你可以通过访问
preferredConstantSizeCategory
preferredConstantSizeCategory
property on either your view's
属性在你的界面的
traitCollection or on the
traitCollection 上或是
UIApplication object.
UIApplication 对象上完成这一点
The default text size will
默认字体大小会
return large and the standard
返回 large 标准大小
sizes run from extra small to
会从 extra small 变成
extra, extra, extra large.
extra extra extra large
The Accessibility sizes are
辅助功能中的大小
prefixed with Accessibility to
会加上前缀 Accessibility 来避免
avoid adding more extras.
要一直加 extra
Now, in iOS 11 we've added new
现在在 iOS 11 中我们添加了
functions that you can use to
新的功能你可以用来
ask questions about the user's
询问用户的
text size.
字体大小
So, for example, you can check
举个例子你可以查看
whether the user is using one of
用户是否正在使用
the Accessibility text sizes,
辅助功能中的字体大小
and if so, you can do an
如果是的话你可以
alternate layout like vertical
提供一个备用界面比如垂直堆叠界面
or you can use any threshold you
或者你可以使用任何你想用的临界值
We now support compares in
我们现在支持在
operators so you can check
操作中进行比较这样你就可以
whether the user's text size is
确认用户的字体大小
larger than a particular
是否大于某个临界值
So that covers some general
这就是一些
guidelines for adapting your
将你的视图适应于
layouts for Dynamic Type.
Dynamic Type 的基本参考
Now let's look at the specific
现在我们来看一个桌面视图的
case of table views.
具体例子
Earlier we saw how the Settings
之前我们看到了
app adapts beautifully for all
设置 app 是如何完美适应
Dynamic Type sizes.
Dynamic Type 字体的
The good news is that if you're
好消息是如果你使用
using a standard table view
一个标准的桌面视图样式
styles, you will get this kind
你可以免费获得
of layout for free.
这样的界面
So your fonts will grow or
那样你的字体就会变大
shrink, depending on the Dynamic
或缩小取决于 Dynamic
Type setting, and for larger
Type 的设置对于较大的字体
fonts the text will wrap so that
文字就会自动换行确保
all of it is visible.
全部文字都可见
Also, for standard table views
另外对于有详细的文字标签的
that have a detail text label,
桌面视图
those will automatically lay out
它们会自动的变成
with vertical stacking for
垂直堆叠视图
larger fonts.
在大字体的情况下
So standard table views will
那么标准的桌面视图将会
adapt their layout for Dynamic
将它们的界面适应于 Dynamic
Type, and cell heights are based
Type 单元高度取决于
on their content.
它们的内容
This is particularly important
这在大字体情况下
at larger font sizes where the
文字的自动换行
text wraps because a cell that
尤其重要因为一个单元
has more text may need to be
如果有较多文字的话可能需要
taller than a cell that has
比一个有较少内容的单元的高度高一些
less.
那么我们如何在桌面视图中实现
cell heights in a table view?
可变的单元高度呢
We can do this through a
我们可以通过
technique called self-sizing.
一种叫做 self-sizing 的技术实现
When self-sizing is enabled, the
当打开 self-sizing 时
table view will ask each cell to
桌面视图会让每个单元
provide its own size and the
提供它的大小
cell can calculate that based on
而每个单元可以依据自己的
its own content.
内容多少而进行计算
Then the table view client
然后桌面视图监控端
simply needs to give the table
就只需要给予
view an estimate for any cells
桌面视图一个有哪些单元
that are off screen.
没有出现在屏幕上的估算
In iOS 11 self-sizing is enabled
在 iOS 11 中 self-sizing 是默认打开的
However, if you're using fixed
然而如果你使用固定的
row heights or if you are using
行高度或者如果你使用
Interface Builder, you may need
Interface Builder 你可能需要去
to enable self-sizing.
打开 self-sizing
To do so set your row height of
你只需要把你的
a table view to be Automatic
桌面视图的行高度设置成 Automatic
Dimension and then set the
Dimension 然后把
Estimated Row Height to a
Estimated Row Height 设置成一个 to a
reasonable estimate given your
给予你的桌面视图的合理估测值
If you have section headers and
如果你的每部分有页眉和
footers, you can do the same
页脚你可以进行相同的操作
thing for those using very
只要使用名字
similarly named properties.
很相似的属性就可以
So that's the story for standard
这就是关于标准桌面视图
table view cells.
单元的内容
Now, if you're using custom
如果你使用自定义单元
cells with Auto Layout, it's
和 Auto Layout 很容易
really easy to get these to work
就可以使它们与
with self-sizing.
self-sizing 一起工作
All you need to do is set up
你所要做的就只是
your constraints so that they
设置好你的限制条件
define the size of the cell and
使它们来定义单元的大小
then Auto Layout will figure out
然后 Auto Layout 就会帮你找到
the size for you.
合适的大小
So let's look at how we could
那么让我们看看
set up the constraints for this
如何才能为这个自定义的单元
custom cell shown here, where we
设置限制
have two labels, one on top of
这其中我们有两个标签一个在另一个
the other.
的上面
We'll definitely want leading
我们肯定是想要为
and trailing constraints for
这两个标签设置前后两个限制
And we want to make sure that
并且我们要确保
the labels are separated
这两个标签是垂直分开的
vertically by an appropriate
中间有合适的间隔
Again, you can use the new
你可以再次使用新的
System Spacing Constraints to
System Spacing Constraints
get a value that will work well
来获得一个在任何字体下
at all text sizes.
都可用的值
So are we done?
那么这样做就可以了吗
Not quite.
并不是
We still need to add constraints
我们还需要增加
relative to the top and bottom
相对于单元的顶部和底部
of the cell and that will
的限制并使它
complete the set of constraints
完成我们所需要的
we need to define the size of
定义单元大小的
the cell.
一组限制条件
Again, you can use the System
你可以再一次使用这里的 System
Spacing Constraints here to get
Spacing Constraints here 来获取
values that will look good
在各个字体大小下
across all text sizes.
都看起来美观的值
Now, if you're using Manual
如果你对你的单元使用 Manual
Layout with your cells, you can
Layout 你还可以
also use self-sizing.
使用 self-sizing
To do so you'll want to override
你需要重写你的单元
the sizeThatFits method on your
sizeThatFits 功能
cell, and then you can use the
然后你可以使用
contentView's width to figure
contentView 的宽度来
out the width available for your
找到你的子视图可用的宽度
Now let's move on to our last
现在让我们开始我们的
topic, images.
最后一个话题图像
Why are images showing up in a
为什么图像会出现在
talk about Dynamic Type?
一个关于 Dynamic Type 的演讲中呢
After all, they're not text.
毕竟它们不是文字
But images are an integral part
但是图像是
of your app's UI and in some
你的 app 的 UI 中不可或缺的一部分
cases they carry meaning that's
有时候它们所承载的意义并不能在
not communicated elsewhere.
其他地方传达
So for the same reason it's
所以与为什么
important for your text to be
你的文字对你的用户而言
readable by your users, it's
可读性高很重要一样
also important that your images
你的图像的可分辨性
are distinguishable.
也非常重要
Let's look at an example.
我们来看一个例子
So here's the Recents view in
这是电话 app 中的最近通话界面
Notice how in front of some of
请注意在有些记录的前面
the calls there's an image of a
有一个电话的图像
phone with an arrow pointing out
还有一个向外的箭头
This image means that this call
这个图像表示的是
was made by you versus a call
这通电话是你打出的而不是
that came in.
一个别人打进的电话
Now let's turn up the text size.
现在让我们调大字号
For those of you who are
对于你们中好奇的人
wondering, the image has moved
这个图像已经被移动
over here and notice how it is
到了这里请注意
tiny compared to the text.
与文字相比它非常小
If you need your text to be this
如果你想要你的文字变成这么大
big so you can read it, you
以至于你可以阅读那么你
probably can't see that image.
或许无法再看到这个图像
So what we really want to do
所以我们真正要做的是
here is scale the image the same
把图像缩放
way that we scale a text, and
到跟文字相同倍数
that's exactly what we've done
而这就正是我们在
in iOS 11, and better yet, we
iOS 11 中所做的更好的是
made it easy for you to do so in
我们让你在自己的 app 中进行这种操作
your own apps.
变得简单
So to just allow your images to
要使你的图像
scale for Dynamic Type you'll
为 Dynamic Type 缩放你需要
first want to make sure that
首先确保
your images are provided as
你的图像在 1x 大的时候是 PDF 格式
So this is a good idea anyways
这无论如何都是一个好主意
because it allows you to use the
因为它允许你在
same image for both 2x and 3x
2x 和 3x 分辨率的设备上使用
resolution devices.
同一个图像
In fact, your app might already
事实上你的 app 可能已经
be doing this.
在这么做了
So just make sure you have a
所以只要确保你的格式是 PDF 的
Next, go to the Asset Catalog
下一步到 Asset Catalog 中
and check this new checkbox for
勾选这个新的选项即
Preserving Vector Data.
Preserving Vector Data
If you don't check the checkbox,
如果你没有勾选它
when the Asset Catalog is
那么在 Asset Catalog 被
compiled, it's going to
编辑时它将
rasterize all the PDF's.
栅格化所有 PDF 的数据
But if you check the checkbox,
但如果你勾选了这个选项
the original PDF gets preserved,
原始 PDF 就可以得到保存
and the cool thing about that is
这样做很酷的一点就是
that now if you use this image
此时如果你使用这个图像
and put it into an image view of
并把它放入任何大小的图像视图
any size, the image will get
这个图像就会
drawn smoothly using PDF
用 PDF 平滑延展
Drawing.
延展中
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
Now, the final step is to make
现在最后一步是
sure that your view resizes for
确保你的界面为
Dynamic Type.
Dynamic Type 更改了大小
To do this in Interface Builder
在 Interface Builder 中
you can select any image view or
你可用选择任何图像视图或者
button and you can check the new
按钮并且你可以选择
Adjusts Image Size property.
Adjusts Image Size 属性
This means that your image
这意味着你的图像按钮
viewer button will scale up for
将会为
the five largest Dynamic Type
五个最大的 Dynamic Type 字体进行缩放
And you can do the same thing in
你也可以用代码完成
code with the Adjusts Image Size
对 AccessibilityContentSizeCategory 属性
for
使用 Adjusts Image Size
AccessibilityContentSizeCategory
功能
There's one more place where
还有一个地方
image scaling comes in handy,
图像缩放会派上用场
and that's when the user long
就是当用户长按
presses on a bar item.
标签栏按钮时
So earlier we saw how you can
之前我们看到你可用
long press on the Voicemail tab
长按“语音信箱”按钮
to show a larger version in the
看到一个更大的图像出现在
middle of the screen.
屏幕的中间
Notice that both the text is
请注意文字和图片
scaling and also the image.
都进行了缩放
So we want to make sure that
我们需要确保
that image looks as good as
图像看起来尽可能的好
If your bar item is using a PDF
如果你的标签栏按钮使用了 PDF
image, all you need to do is
图像那么你需要做的就是
check the Preserve Vector Data
勾选 Preserve Vector Data
checkbox that we saw earlier.
选项
That will allow UIKit to scale
这将允许 UIKit 把它
it up smoothly.
顺利地的放大
If you're not using a PDF,
如果你没有使用 PDF 格式
you'll want to provide a larger
你就需要提供一个更大的版本
version that we can show when
让它在用户
the user long presses on that
长按图像时显示
To do that in Interface Builder
要在 Interface Builder 操作
you can go to the Attributes
你可以找到 Attributes
Inspector and set the
Inspector 然后把你的标签栏的 and set the
Accessibility property of your
Accessibility 属性
bar item to be the larger
设置成更大的版本
Or in code you can simply set
或者在代码中你可以把
the largeContentSizeImage
largeContentSizeImage
property to that larger version.
属性设置成那个更大版本
So we've just covered a variety
我们已经谈到了一些
of tips and tricks you can use
建议和窍门
to adapt your apps for Dynamic
让你的 app 能适应 Dynamic Type
And now I'd like to invite
现在我想有请
Nandini to the stage to show all
Nandini 到台上来在一个
of that in a sample app.
示范 app 中展示
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Hi everyone.
&gt;&gt; 大家好
I'm Nandini.
我是 Nandini
I'm a software engineer in the
我是苹果辅助功能团队的
Accessibility Team at Apple.
一名软件工程师
Today, using a sample app, I'll
今天我会用一个示范 app
show you how you can fix your
展示如何在
app in very little time with
短时间内用 Dynamic Type 字体
[inaudible] font sizes.
修正你的 app
First, I will open the app in
首先我先用
the default text size, and later
默认字体大小打开 app
I'll open the app in the largest
稍后我会用最大号的
of the Dynamic Type font size
Dynamic Type 字体打开
and fix issues along the way.
然后解决其中的问题
Let's start the app.
让我们来打开 app
We cleared it.
我们已经清理过了
It's called Cute Battle Pets.
它叫 Cute Battle Pets
In this app you can choose among
在这个 app 中你可以选择
two pets to battle with each
两只宠物来对战
Let me open the app now.
让我来打开 app
In this tab, Opponents, you see
在这个部分 Opponents 你可以看到
a list of pets you can choose to
一些宠物你可用从中选择
battle among each other, and the
进行对战在下一个
next tab, Achievements, you see
部分 Achievements 你可以看到
a list of badges of honors these
一些这些宠物获得的奖章
Before auditing our app for the
在我们使用
largest of the Dynamic Type font
Dynamic Type 的最大号字体来审核
size, if we switch back to the
我们的 app 之前如果我们切换回刚刚的
Opponents tab, you can audit
Opponents 按钮你可以用
your app for the largest of the
一个在 Xcode 中非常好用的工具
Dynamic Font size using a very
来测试你的 app 在不同字体下的效果
handy tool in Xcode called
这个工具叫做
Accessibility Inspector.
Accessibility Inspector
This tool is very handy because
这个工具非常好用
you can audit your app before
因为你可以
going to the Settings app on
在更改你的设备的设置之前
your device.
测试你的 app
You can open this tool by going
你可以通过在菜单栏进入
to Xcode in the menu bar, choose
Xcode 打开这个工具
Open Developer Tool and then
选择 Open Developer Tool 然后
click on Accessibility
点击 Accessibility Inspector
This tool can be used to audit
这个工具可以被用于
apps in all macOS and iOS
在所有的 macOS 和 iOS 手机中测试你的 app
iPhones, including the
包括模拟机
As our app is running on the
因为我们的 app 现在在
iPhone Simulator, I'll choose
iPhone 模拟机上运行我从
Start from the dropdown menu.
下拉菜单中选择 Simulator
I'll go to the Settings tab in
我在 Accessibility Inspector 点击设置键
Here you see a font size slider.
在这里你可以看到一个字体大小的滑块
The font size is currently the
现在的字体是
default text size.
默认的字体大小
I'm going to move the slider's
我要把滑块
knob to the last notch on the
移到最右边
That is the largest of the
就是最大的
Dynamic Type font size.
Dynamic Type 字体
Let's go back to our app now to
让我们现在回到我们的 app
see the effect of this change.
来看看这个改变带来的效果
The font size of these labels
这些标签的字体大小
has not changed yet.
还没有改变
Any idea why this is happening?
知道为什么会这样吗
This is happening because of two
有两个原因
The labels here are not yet set
这些标签还没有被设置为
to automatically adjust to the
自动调整以适应
user's ContentSizeCategory, and
用户的 ContentSizeCategory
the petName and petDescription
并且 petName 和 petDescription
labels here are using custom
标签使用的是自定义字体
Let's go to a project now to fix
我们现在启动一个项目来
these issues.
解决这些问题
I'll minimize Accessibility
我现在把 Accessibility
Inspector for now.
Inspector 最小化
I'll go to BattleCell zip file.
打开 BattleCell 压缩文件
Here, using the jump bar, I'll
使用跳转栏
move to Set Up Labels and
跳转到 Set Up 标签和
Buttons Method.
Buttons 功能
Here for petName, petDescription
对于 petName petDescription
and battleButton's titleLabel,
和 battleButton's titleLabel 标签
I'll set the property at this
把这个字体在
font for ContentSizeCategory and
ContentSizeCategory 的属性
I'll set it to True.
设置为 True
As petName and petDescription
由于 petName 和 petDescription
are using custom fonts, we can
使用的是自定义字体
use UIFont, make it API, scan
我们可以使用 UIFont 设置为 API 来扫描
font for font metric.
字体以获得字体规格
For petName I'll be using the
对于 petName 我把 Textstyle
headline TextStyle.
设为 headline
For petDescription I'll be using
对于 petDescription 我把 Textstype
the sub headline TextStyle.
设为 subheadline
Let's run the app again and see
我们来重新运行一下 app
the effect of these changes.
看看这些更改带来的变化
Now, after these labels are
现在当这些标签都被
adjusted to the user's
调整以适应用户的
ContentSizeCategory, we see that
ContentSizeCategory 后我们可以看到
these labels have really less
这些标签没有足够的
horizontal room to grow.
横向空间
With the menu on the left and
菜单在左边而
the button on the right, these
按钮在右边的情况下
labels have really less
这些标签并没有足够的
horizontal room to grow and the
横向空间进行放大
labels either truncate or wrap
并且要么被截断了
in multiple lines.
要么被分成很多行
We can fix this by having an
我们可以通过一个
alternate adopt layout for
使用更大字体的备用界面结构
larger text constraints.
来解决这个问题
We can achieve this by moving
我们可以通过把
the image above the text and the
图片移动到文字上方而
button below the text.
按钮移动到文字下方来实现
This will ensure that the labels
这样就可以保证标签更少的发生
are less of wrap and truncated.
换行和截断的情况
Let's go fix this in our project
我们现在到项目中解决这个问题
First, before adding this
首先为了更大字体要添加这个
adoptLayoutConstraints for
adoptLayoutConstraints 之前
larger text constraints, let me
我需要先
add a private variable for that.
为它添加一个私有变量
Next let me go to
下一步选择
setupLayoutConstraints method.
setupLayoutConstraints 功能
Here you see that you already
现在你可以看到
have a set of layout constraints
你已经有了一些对于默认字体大小的
for default text size.
界面限制
Now I'll be placing a set of
现在我要设置一些
constraints for larger Dynamic
对于较大的
Type font sizes.
Type 的字体大小的限制
These set of constraints pasted
这些被加到这里的限制
here will be available in the
会和示范 app 的代码
sample app code attached along
一起出现在
the session website.
这个会议的网站上
You can go and review this after
会议结束以后你可以到网站上查看
the session, but I give a short
但我会简单地
overview of what this actually
介绍一下它们是做什么的
These constraints ensure that
这些限制可以确保
the image labels and the button
图像标签和按钮
are vertically stacked, and
是垂直堆叠的
these constraints also get them
也可以把它们放入
in the height of the cell.
单元高度中
Okay. Let's go to our
好了我们看到
developerLayoutConstraints
developerLayoutConstraints 功能
Here we see that one of the
在这里我们看到
developer constraints aren't
有一个开发者限制没有被启用
We need the larger [inaudible],
我们需要更大的字体对吧
right.
让我们来解决它
Here, based on user's
这样根据用户的
preferredContentSizeCategory,
preferredContentSizeCategory
they put in the five largest
这些代码添加了五个最大的
Dynamic Type font sizes.
Dynamic Type 字体
With the app you will be able to
使用 app 你应该可以
look at its constraints and
看到它的限制和
activateLargeTextConstraints.
activateLargeTextConstraints.
Otherwise, do the reverse
否则就采取相反操作
To ensure that these layout
为了保证这些界面
constraints are up-to-date based
限制能够
on the change in trait
根据 trait collection 的变化而
collection, we call this method
变化
if trait collection did change.
如果 trait collection 发生变化我们就使用这个功能
If the user's
如果用户的
preferredContentSizeCategory
preferredContentSizeCategory
shifts from the five largest
从最大的五个
Dynamic Type font sizes to the
Dynamic Type 字体更换为
smaller Dynamic Type font sizes,
较小的 Dynamic Type 字体
or visa-versa, these layout
或者反过来这些界面限制
constraints will be updated.
就会被更新
Let's run the app again to see
我们来重新运行一下 app 来看看
the effect of these changes.
这些改变的效果
Great. After vertically stacking
很好在把内容垂直堆叠以后
the content the labels are less
标签就没有那么多
of wrapped and there's no
被分行的情况
truncation at all.
并且没有被截断的情况
Let's go the next step,
我们进行下一步
Achievements.
Achievements 部分
When we run the app in the
当我们在默认字体情况下
default text size, you will
运行这个 app 时你会
notice that these cells here
注意到这些单元
have multiple lines of text, but
有很多行文字
currently only one line of text
但是现在只有一行文字
is visible on screen.
可以在屏幕上可见
Let's go to Achievements View
我们到 Achievements View
Controller in Swift check on why
Controller 看看
this is happening.
为什么会这样
This is happening because the
之所以会发生这样的情况是因为
table view's row height is set
桌面视图的行高度被设置成了
to a constant value, hundred.
一个恒定的值 100
This makes that these cells do
这导致了这些单元
not have cell size at all.
根本没有单元大小
To fix this and make this cells
为了解决这个问题让这些单元
have size we have to set the
具有大小我们需要把
table view's row height to use
桌面视图的行高度设置为使用
UITableViewAutomaticDimension,
UITableViewAutomaticDimension
and TableView's
并把 TableView's
estimatedRowHeight to a constant
estimatedRowHeight 设为一个恒定值
value, and I'll choose hundred.
我会选择 100
Let's run the app again.
我们再重新运行一下 app
Let me go to Achievements tab.
选择 Achievements 部分
Now we see that we have more
现在我们看到
lines of text in each of these
在每个单元里我们都有了更多行文字
cells, and the cells, they're
这些单元的大小都
sized to fit content, but let's
设置为适应内容的多少但是
take a look at the [inaudible].
让我们来看看文字前面的图标
Unlike the labels the images do
与文字不同这些图标并没有
not grow, according to the
随着用户的 ContentSizeCategory
user's ContentSizeCategory.
而变大
To fix this let's go to
要解决这个问题我们打开
Achievements [inaudible] file.
Achievements 文件
And set the label and image view
设置标签和图像视图功能
For the badgeImageView I set the
对于 badgeImageView 我把
property adjustsImageSize for
accessibilityContentSize Category
accessibilityContentSize
的属性 adjustsImageSize
Category, and I set it to two.
设置为 True
This will ensure that the image
这能保证图像
is scaled for the five largest
会随着五个最大的
Dynamic Type font sizes.
Dynamic Type 字体而缩放
Let's run the app again to see
我们再一次运行一下 app
the effect of this change.
来看看变化的效果
Let me move to Achievements tab.
打开 Achievements 选项
Great. Both the labels and the
很好现在文字和
image have sizes largest Dynamic
图像都是最大的 Dynamic
Type font size, but let's take a
Type 字号但是让我们看到
closer look at the image in
这些单元中的图像
Let's also take a look at the
我们也来看一看
large text only that comes up in
只有在长按标签栏图标才会弹出的
a long press on the tab bar
大字体
Based on that, the images in
这样看起来这些
these cells and also in the tab
单元中的图像和标签栏的
bar icons were not smooth.
图标不够顺滑
To fix that we have to go to
为了解决问题我们需要到
Assets Catalog, choose our
Assets Catalog 选择我们的
images, those are PDF images, go
图像都是 PDF 图像然后到
to the Attributes Inspector and
Attributes Inspector 并
click on the Preserve Vector
点击 Preserve Vector
Data checkbox.
Data 选项
If we do this, what happens is
这样做之后
the PDF vector data is preserved
PDF 向量数据就被保存了
and the images are rendered
图像就会在
smooth in different Dynamic Type
不同的 Dynamic Type 字体中
font sizes.
都平滑呈现
Let's run the app again to see
我们来重新运行一下 app
the effect of this change.
看看效果
Let me go to Achievements tab.
打开 Achievements 选项
For confirmation, let me zoom in
为了进一步确认让我放大一下
Now we see that the images here
现在我们看到这些图像都
are rendered smooth, right.
平滑呈现了对吧
Finally, using the Accessibility
最后使用 Accessibility
Inspector, I'm going to run
Inspector 我要做一个
through a quick audit of this
快速的测试
app and different Dynamic Type
测试这个 app 和不同 Dynamic Type
font sizes.
字体
For that let me minimize Xcode.
让我先最小化 Xcode
Let me bring up the
让我打开
Accessibility Inspector.
Accessibility Inspector
Let me move the first tab,
打开第一个选项
Opponents.
Opponents
Let me switch the font size
把字体大小的滑块
slider to default text size.
滑到默认字体大小
Now I'm going to increase the
现在我要一个一个的
font size one-by-one and you'll
增大字体然后你会
notice that the labels in these
看到这些单元中的标签
cells increase according to the
会根据
user's ContentSizeCategory.
用户 ContentSizeCategory 而变大
When I move to the five larger
当我把滑块移动到最大的五个
Dynamic Type font sizes, the
Dynamic Type 字体时
layout of these cells change.
这些单元的界面发生了改变
The labels have more horizontal
这些标签有了更多的
room to grow and the cell says
横向空间这些单元也改变大小
sizeToFitContent.
来适应内容的多少
Next move on to Achievements to
下一步我们打开 Achievements 来
do the same audit.
进行同样的测试
I'll switch back to default text
我要重新切换到默认字体大小
size.
然后一个一个的增大字体
Now, you see that the labels
现在你可以看到
wrap in multiple lines.
标签已经自动换行
The cell says sizeToFitContent,
这些单元也自动改变大小来适应内容
and also the image scales in the
同时图像也
five larger Dynamic Type font
按照最大的五个 Dynamic Type 字体进行缩放
So there you have it.
这样你就达到了目的
Our app looks pretty great in
我们的 app 在
all the Dynamic Type font sizes.
各种 Dynamic Type 字体下都看起来不错
So using the new API's available
所以使用 iOS 11 提供的新的 API
in iOS 11, you can make your
你也可以让自己的 app
apps, too, work for all Dynamic
适应所有的 Dynamic
Type font sizes.
Type 字体大小
Now I welcome Clare back on
现在请 Clare 回来
stage to conclude the
做一个总结
presentation.
谢谢
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, Nandini.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 Nandini
So all of that sample code is
所有的示范代码
available on our session
都可以在
website, but the version we have
会议的网站找到
on the session website is
但是我们的版本
actually expanded to include
实际上被扩展了包括了
even more examples.
更多的例子
So you can see how we do this in
所以你可以看到我们如何
Interface Builder.
处理 Interface Builder 的
You can see an example where we
你可以找到我们是如何
wrap text around images.
让文字环绕图片的
You can find a case where we
你可以看到我们
allow scrolling only when
只在大字体必要时
necessary for larger fonts, and
允许滚动等等
Think of it as a recipe book for
把它当成一个菜谱用来帮助你
things you might encounter in
处理你在自己的 app 中
your own apps.
可能遇到的问题
So we highly encourage you to
我们强烈建议你
check it out after the session.
在会议结束后查看
To summarize what we covered
总结一下我们今天讨论的内容
today, it's easy to support
使用新的 API 会使
Dynamic Type with new API in iOS
在 iOS 11 中支持 Dynamic Type 变得很简单
If you have an app that doesn't
如果你的 app 不支持
support Dynamic Type, now is a
Dynamic Type 现在是让它
great time to do so, and you
支持的好时候
should because supporting
你应该这么做因为支持
Dynamic Type is good for your
Dynamic Type 是对你的用户有好处的
It's good for the users who
它对喜欢
prefer smaller text because it
更小的字体的用户有好处因为它
allows them to see more on
允许他们可以在屏幕上看到更多内容
It's good for the users who
也对喜欢
prefer larger text because it's
更大字体的用户有好处因为它
more comfortable to read, and
阅读起来更舒适
it's especially beneficial for
并且它对
users who need larger text in
需要更大字体以使他们能够阅读的用户
order to be able to read it.
更加是福利性的
When more apps are usable by
当更多的 app 可以给
people with a disability, such
残疾人使用时比如
as low vision, it really helps
视力低下的人它真的
to level the playing field for
为这些人提供了一个更公平的环境
And so by supporting Dynamic
所以在你的 app 中支持 Dynamic
Type in your app, you're
Type 你也正在把
actually making the world a
这个世界变得更好
So we really hope you take what
所以我们真的希望你能够
you saw today in today's session
了解你今天所看到的一切
and go back and make apps that
回去开发一些
work well with Dynamic Type and
适用 Dynamic Type 的 app 然后
include more users so that more
包含更多的用户这样
users can benefit from the great
更多的用户才可以从
work you've done.
你的杰出工作中获益
For more information, including
如果想了解更多信息
the sample code we showed,
包括今天我们展示的案例
please go to our session
请查看我们的网站
Now, there have been several
现在这次会议已经
sessions at this conference
有几场讨论
related to the one we just gave.
跟我们刚才谈的内容有关
As we mentioned earlier, the
正如我们之前提到的那样
Design for Everyone talk from
昨天的 Design for Everyone 会议
yesterday covers the design
讨论了 iOS 11 的 Dynamic Type 进步背后
thinking behind the iOS 11
的设计理念
There are also two sessions on
也有两场关于
accessibility, What's New in
辅助功能的会议 What's New in
Accessibility and Media and
Accessibility 和 Media and
Gaming Accessibility.
Gaming Accessibility
Both of these sessions cover how
这两场会议都讨论了
you can widen your user base and
你可以如何扩大你的用户基础和
include more users.
包含更多用户
And finally, as we mentioned
最后正如我们之前提到的
earlier, to learn more about the
想了解更多关于
System Spacing Constraints in
System Spacing Constraints 在
Interface Builder, check out the
Interface Builder 中的内容请查看
Auto Layout Techniques in
Auto Layout Techniques in
Interface Builder talk.
Interface Builder 会议
Thank you all for coming, and I
谢谢你们来到这里
hope you enjoy the rest of the
我希望你们能够享受接下来的会议
[ Applause ]
[掌声]